

yaroslav.khudchenko@gmail.com 🔀

+48 796 845 798

Wroclaw, Poland 💡

linkedin.com/in/yaroslavkhudchenko in

github.com/YariPL 🕠

Front-end developer with almost 2 years of hands-on experience in developing web applications as well as mobile and desktop ones. On a daily basis working with javascript frameworks like React.js, Ember.js and css preprocessors like SASS. Have experience in creating desktop solutions with Electron and mobile Progressive Web Apps.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front-end developer Lune.xyz

07/2018 – Present AR & VR apps Wrocław

Tasks

- Developing web applications
- Creating commercial web pages
- Developing and maintaining existing systems
- Working with Three.js and WebAR

Part-time PHP programmer link2light

07/2017 – 12/2017 SEO company Lublin

- Tasks
- Automation of the e-shop
- Working with databases
- Using phpMyAdmin / X-Cart

EDUCATION

International Relations

University of Maria Curie-Sklodovska

10/2016 - 06/2018

- Thesis
- Cybersecurity
 Dilemma in the
 Context of Edward
 Snowden's Case

International Relations (in Polish) University of Maria Curie-Sklodowska

10/2013 - 06/2016

SKILLS

JavaScript React.js Ember.js RWD

SASS GIT PWA Webpack Three.js

NPM HTML/CSS Electron

ACHIEVEMENTS

Front-End Web Developer Nanodegree - Udacity (02/2018 – 08/2018)

I have received the grant for this program after successfully completing the Google Developer Scholarship.

CERTIFICATES

Front End Libraries - FreeCodeCamp (03/2019)
☑

JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures - FreeCodeCamp (11/2018) ☑

Responsive Web Design - FreeCodeCamp (01/2018) ♂

Google Developer Challenge Scholarship (11/2017 – 02/2018)

LANGUAGES

English			0
Polish			0
Ukrainian			
Russian			